Finding Aid for Rensis Likert papers, 1929-1983.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Bureau of Agricultural Economics
  - Reports and memoranda
    - 1944
      - Home Gardens and Home Preservation of Foods, Study 107, 12/1944 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Home Gardens and Home Preservation of Foods. Study 107. Background File, 12/1944 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - The September Nutrition Campaign: A survey of its effect. Study 107-II, 12/1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Motivation and the Sale of Bonds, Special Report, 1/12/1944 (Box 23)
      - Summary of the Results of the Fourth War Loan Drive, 4/5/1944 (Box 23)
      - Memorandum: Review of the Preliminary State Reports on Post-war Programs, 4/22/1944 (Box 23)
      - "Two Problems in the Use of the Open Question" (Box 24)
    - 1945
      - The Dairy Subsidy as Farmers See It: An analysis of the views of farmers in the Corn Belt and in the Great Lakes and Northeast dairy areas, based on Studies 102 and 105, 1/1945 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Memorandum: Recommendations on the problem of selling bonds after the fall of Germany, 5/4/1945 (Box 23)
      - Memorandum, "Experimental Study of Two Methods of Coding" (Box 24)
      - Roster of Regular Studies (#1-130) (Box 24)
    - 1943-1946
      - Treasury Department Studies, 2 volumes (Box 24)
      - Treasury Department Studies, 1 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1946
      - Public Attitudes toward Farm-City Parity: A Pilot Study Based on a Sample of Farmers and City Dwellers in Three Southern States, Study 104, 1/1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Farmers' Views on Postwar Programs for Cotton: A Survey in the Cotton Belt, Study 111 (Preliminary Report), 1/1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - A Study of Liquid Assets: Sample Interviews collected in Birmingham, Alabama and Douglas County, Illinois, Study 113, 2/1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - A Study of Liquid Assets. Study 113. Background file, 2/1949 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - The Postwar Outlook for a Farm-Based Community: A Survey of Augusta County, Virginia. Section I-A. The Postwar Labor Force B. Plans for Postwar Expenditures, 2/1945 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Appraisal of the Sixth War Loan, Part I: Solicitation and Buying. Preliminary Tabulations, Study No. 118-1, 2/01/1945 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Appraisal of the Sixth War Loan. Background files, 2/01/1945 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Appraisal of the Sixth War Loan--Part II: Identification and Motivation (Preliminary Tabulations), Study No. 112-11, 2/01/1945 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Farmers' Views on Postwar Programs for Cotton: A survey in the Cotton Belt, Study 111-II, 3/1945 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Impact of O.P.A. Enforcement Activities on Food Wholesalers: Sample Interviews from the Protest in New York and Baltimore. Study 120, 3/1945 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Impact of O.P.A. Enforcement Activities on Food Wholesalers. Study 120. Background files, 3/1945 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Veterans Readjustment to Civilian Life. Study 109, 3/02/1945 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - An Analysis of War Bond Redemptions. Study No. 118-III, 3/07/1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Memorandum: The Impact of OPA Enforcement Activities on Food Wholesalers, 3/21/1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Veterans Readjustment to Civilian Life. Study No. 109, 3/23/1945 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Home Preservation of Fruits and Vegetables in, 1944; 4/1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - The Postwar Outlook for Bonds: A Survey of Industrial Workers in Detroit. Study No. 112, 4/05/1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Consumer Acceptance of Dried Milk in Houston, Texas. Study 116-II, 5/04/1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Grocers' Experiences in Selling Dried Milk in Houston, Texas. Study 116/II, 5/04/1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Dried Milk Houston, Texas. Study 116. Background files, 5/04/1945 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - A Study of Liquid Assets: Sample Interviews collected in Birmingham, Alabama and Douglas County, Illinois. Study 113--14 Supplement, 6/09/1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - The Distribution of Liquid Assets: A Pilot Study of Personal Holdings of War Bonds, Bank Deposits, and other Liquid Assets. Study 113-114, 6/11/1945 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - The Distribution of Liquid Assets. Study 113-114. Background files, 6/11/1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Veterans' Readjustment to Civilian Life. Study No. 109, Condensed, 7/16/1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Farmers' Views on Postwar Programs for Wheat. Study 121 (Preliminary Report), 7/31/1945 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Farmers' Views on Postwar Programs for Wheat. Study 121. Background files, 7/31/1945 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Six Farmers Talk About the Wheat Situation. Study 121-II, 8/1945 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Appraisal of the Seventh War Loan. Study No. 128-I, 8/13/1945 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Appraisal of the Seventh War Loan in Chicago. Study No. 128-II, 8/24/1945 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Appraisal of the Seventh War Loan. Study 128. Background files, 8/24/1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Memorandum: Prospects for Spending and Saving by Consumers, 9/15/1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Farmers' Views on Postwar Programs for Wheat: A survey of the major wheat- producing areas. Study 121-III, 10/1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Memorandum: Community Factors in the Land Market, 10-10-1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Attitudes of Rural People Toward Radio Service: Based on a Nationwide Survey. Study 123, 11/1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Attitudes of Rural People Toward Radio Service. Study 123. Background files, 11/1945; 7 folders (Box 4, Folder 3-9)
      - Attitudes of Rural People Toward Radio Service. Study 123. Background files. Proceeding before F.C.C, January 1946 (Box 4, Folder 10-15)
      - The Public's Attitudes Toward Continuation of Bond Sales: A national survey following the Victory Loan. Study 130, 12/1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - The Postwar Sale of Government Bonds. Background files, 12/1945 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Memorandum: Recommendations on the problem of selling bonds after the fall of Germany, 5/4/1945 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Trends in Farm Family Levels and Standards of Living: Prepared by Edgar A. Schular and Rachel Rowe Swiger, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Attitudes Toward FSA Tenant Purchase Program. Study 122, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
      - Attitudes Toward FSA Tenant Purchase Program. Study 122. Background files, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
      - Home Gardens and Home Preserving in 1945. Study 127, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Home Gardens and Home Preserving in 1945. Study 127. Background file, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
      - Appraisal of the Victory Loan: Based on a National Survey. Study 130-III, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Four TP Borrowers, their wives, and Three FSA County Supervisors talk about the Tenant Purchase Program. Study 122, Appendix II, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - FSA County Supervisors talk about the Tenant Purchase Program. Study 122, Appendix II (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Attitudes of Rural People toward Radio Service: a Nation-wide Survey of Farm and Small-town People, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Outlook for the Redemption of Savings Bonds: Based on a national survey following the Victory Loan. Study 130-11, 1/1946 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Generalized Types of Farming in the United States. Delineation on County Boundaries, 1/24/1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Six Families Discuss Their Financial Situation and Financial Plans: Sample Interviews from a National Survey of Liquid Assets. Study 132, 2/1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - The Land Market. Study 126-I, 3/1946 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Home Gardens and Home Preserving in 1945 (with some intentions for 1946), 3/1946 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Appraisal of the Victory Loan Drive. Study 130-III, 4/1930 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Some Highlights of the Research Program Carried on by the Division of Program Surveys for the Treasury Department, 1942-1946; 3/28/1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - How Three People Feel About the International Situation, 4/1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Factors Related to the Amount of Time Rural People Spend Listening to Radio, 4/1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - The Land Market. Study 126, 5/1946 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - The Land Market. Study 126. Background files, 5/1946 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - National Survey of Liquid Asset Holdings, Spending, and Saving. Part one: Major Findings. Study 132-I, 5/1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - National Survey of Liquid Asset Holdings, Spending and Saving. Study 132. Background files, 5/1946 (Box 5, Folder 2-6)
      - Estimates of Quantities of Fruits and Vegetables Preserved in American Homes in, 1945; 5/14/1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - The Land Market: A survey of recent land buyers in the Corn Belt. Study 126-II, 6/1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Appraisal of Postwar Bond Selling: Based on a National Survey. Study 138-I, 9/1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Postwar Bond Redemptions: Based on a National Survey. Study 138-II, 9/1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Postwar Bond Selling: Miscellaneous Memoranda Based on a National Survey Conducted*in July and August 1946. Study 138-III, 10/1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Recent Buyers of Land: Survey of the central corn belt areas of Nebraska, Iowa, and Illinois, 11/1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - The Extension Service in Vermont - Part One: Farmers and the Extension Service, 7/1947 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - An Exploration of Factors Motivating Hog Farmers in Their Production and Marketing, 8/1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - The Extension Service in Vermont - Part Two: Farm Women and the Extension Service, 11/1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - The Extension Service in Vermont. Background files, 11/1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Background files
    - Quarterly Survey of Agriculture.
      - Study 15, 3 folders (Box 5, Folder 15-17)
      - Study 124 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Study 125 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - General Material (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Consumer Acceptance of dehydrated Foods, Grand Rapids, Michigan, Study 17 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Farm Purchases by Industrial Workers. Study 119 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - OPA Community Service Panel Study. Study 129 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - An Exploration of Factors Affecting Farmers' Decisions Regarding Hogs. Study 135., 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - Public Evaluation of the International Situation. Study 137 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - The Postwar Buying and Redeeming of Bonds. Study 138 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Wages and Wage Rates of Hired Farm Workers (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Potato Preferences Among Household Consumers. Study 141 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Food shortage and its Effect on West Coast Morale. Study 64 (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
    - Incomes and Savings in Buffalo. Study 65 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Income-Wage Study, Buffalo, New York. Study 73 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Public Attitudes toward Nurses and Nurse Education (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Victory Loan Survey. Study 130 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Public Experience with Fuel Oil Rationing (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 38-45)
    - Memorandum: Summary of Observations on the Strike of the United Rubber Workers in Akron, Ohio, May 24, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Questionnaires, forms, memoranda, 23 folders (Box 6, Folder 1-23)
    - Notebooks containing questionnaires, forms, memoranda, 4 folders (Box 6, Folder 24-27)
    - Notebooks containing questionnaires, forms, memoranda, 4 folders (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
    - Papers concerning Agricultural Quiz Corner and other exhibit material, 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Survey Division. General administrative memoranda and policy materials (unprocessed) (Box 7)
    - Survey Division. General administrative memoranda and policy materials (unprocessed) (Box 8)
    - Master Sample Survey (unprocessed) (Box 8)
    - War Production Board. Office of Civilian Requirements. Survey Reports (Box 8)
    - National Forest Study (fragmentary) ca., 1941 (Box 23)
    - Milwaukee Conference on Post-war Programs
      - Reports of Committees, July 26-31, 1943 (Box 23)
    - War Loan Drive Studies, ca., 1943-1946 (Box 23)
    - Enumerative Survey of Agriculture, January 1947 (Box 23)
  - Administrative Files
    - General (research summaries, internal memorandum, minutes, organizational chart, etc.), ca., 1942-1945 (Box 23)
    - Annual Report (drafts and background information), 1945 (Box 23)
    - Background to a Proposal for the Administrative Reorganization of the Division of Program Surveys, ca., 1942 (Box 23)
    - Minutes, Military Planning Division, Psychological Research Program, May 9, 1946; June 13, 1946 (Box 23)
  - Survey Research
    - General (methodological proposals, reports and memorandum), ca., 1942-1945 (Box 23)
    - Field Notes and Transcripts of Interviews, 1942-1943 (Box 23)
  - Methodology
    - Coding (memorandum, reports, draft of manual), 1944-1945 (Box 23)
    - Interviews (memorandum, reports, manuals), 1942-1946 (Box 23)
    - Reporting Forms ()., mostly 1944-1946; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Division of Program Surveys
    - Bar Graph of Budget (1940-1946) (Box 23)
    - Memoranda, 1939-1946; 7 folders (Box 23)
    - Methodological Aspects of Division Reserves, 1941-42 (Box 24)
    - Report Draft, 11/12/1945 (Box 24)
    - Study Reliability Report,., 1943-1945 (Box 24)
- Office of War Information
  The series Office of War Information (formerly Office of Facts and Figures) contains copies of the official newsletter Current Surveys, as well as reports and memoranda specifically related to war-time topics. The reports are primarily studies of public perception and reaction to home front policies. Among the topics covered are attitudes toward various ethnic and racial groups, morale, and preliminary perceptions of the post-war world. The materials are arranged chronologically and include correspondence, notes, and related information.
  - Reports and memoranda
    - 1941
      - Summary of Initial Results, 12/19/1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Preliminary Report of Recent Developments, 12/19/1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1942
      - R.2. Report on Recent Developments, 1/05/1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - R.3. Exploratory Study of West Coast Reactions to Japanese, 2/04/1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - R.4. Reactions to Price Control and Rationing, Preliminary Results, 2/09/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Special Report on Negro Housing Situation in Detroit, 3/05/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - R.5. Reactions to the Rubber Situation, Preliminary Results, 2/16/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - R.6. West Coast Reactions to the Japanese Situation, 3/06/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - R.7. Preliminary Appraisal of the Present Negro Situation, 3/09/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - R.8. American Reactions to War Developments, 3/26/1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - R.9. Farmer Morale, 3/31/1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - R. 10. Readiness for Sacrifice, 4/07/1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - R. 11. Reactions to Cost of Living, Price Control, Shortages and Rationing, 4/14/1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Attitudes Affecting War Production, 4/14/1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Memorandum re. The Immediate Reactions to the Fall of Bataan, 4/16/1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Morale in Civilian Defense: A Special Study in San Francisco, 4/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - S.R. 5. Reactions to Posters Regarding Price Regulations, 4/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - R. 12. Workers and the War, 4/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - S.R.6. Summary of Recent Findings, 5/05/1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - S.R.7. Town Meeting for War; Ontario, California, April 25, 1942, 5/7/1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - S.R.8.-March-on Washington Movement among Negroes, 5/12/1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - S.R.9. Effective Appeals in the Buying of War Bonds! Preliminary Data from Baltimore, 5/14/1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - S.R.10. Current Problems of Negro Morale, 5/16/1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - R.13. American Unity, 5/26/1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Preliminary R.14. America Views the Post-War World, 5/26/1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - R.14. America Views the Post-War World, 5/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - S.R.11. Some Labor/Management Problems within the Shipbuilding Industry, 5/29/1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - S.R.12. The Buying of War Bonds and Stamps, 6/02/1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - R-15. The Axis Line in America (not issued), 6/09/1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - R.16. Reactions to the War Economy, 6/16/1942 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - R.16. Reactions to the War Economy. Background files, 6/16/1942 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - S.R.13. Enemy Alien Minorities in Eastern Cities, 6/22/1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - The "Problem" of Enemy Aliens on the East Coast, 6/23/1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - R.15a. The Grievance Pattern: Elements of Disunity in America, 6/25/1942 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - S.R. 14. Reader Reactions to Treasury Pamphlet Our America, 6/25/1942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Preliminary Report. Worker Reactions to War Production Within Local Plant Situations, 7/07/1942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - R.17. Worker Reactions to Incentives Used in War Industries, 7/1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - R.17a. Summary Report. Worker Reactions to Incentives Used in War Industries, 7/07/1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - R.18. Control of Wages, Hours and Profits in the Furthering of War Production, 7/07/1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - R.18a. Summary Report. Control of Wages, Hours and Profits in the Furthering of War Production, 7/07/1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Study 48. The Farmer and the War: Preliminary Results from Three Corn Belt Counties, 7/09/1942 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - S.R.15. The Farmer in the War Economy, 7/14/1942 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - R.19. The Farmer's Machinery and Transportation Problems, 7/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - R.19a. Summary Report. The Farmer's Machinery and Transportation Problems, 7/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - S.R.16. Negroes and the War: A Study in Baltimore and Cincinnati, 7/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - S.R.16a. Summary Report / Negroes and the War: etc, 7/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - R.20. Worker Motivation in Time of War: Case Studies of Six Critical War Plants, 7/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - R.20a. Summary Report. Worker Motivation in Time of War: Case Studies of Six Critical War Plants, 7/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - R.21. The War Worker's Point of View, 7/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - R.21a. Summary Report. The War Worker's Point of View, 7/28/1942 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - S.R.17. Attitudes Toward the Employment of Women in War Industries, 8/04/1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - S.R.18. Reactions to Russian Reverses, 8/05/1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - S.R.19. War Attitudes of the Spanish-Speaking People in the Southwest, 8/11/1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - R.22. The American Public and Selective Service, 8/18/1942 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - R.22a. Summary Report. The American Public and Selective Service, 8/18/1942 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - R.23. Mobilizing American Manpower, 8/18/1942 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - R.23a. Summary Report. Mobilizing American Manpower, 8/18/1942 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Income and Savings in Buffalo. Preliminary Report, 8/22/1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Income and Savings in Buffalo. Background files, 8/22/1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Motives and Attitudes that Influence Thinking About the Post-War World (Preliminary Report), 9/01/1942 (Box 9, Folder 26a)
      - S.R.20. Attitudes Toward Payroll Deductions: The Proposed Withholding Tax and Increased Social Security, 9/04/1942 (Box 9, Folder 26a)
      - R. 24. Public Responses to Economic Controls, 9/08/1942 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - R.24a. Summary Report. Public Responses to Economic Controls, 9/08/1942 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - S.R.21. Wartime Rumors in Two Eastern Cities, 9/12/1942 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - S.R.21a. Appendix: Wartime Rumors in Two Eastern Cities, 9/12/1942 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - S.R.22. Review of the Findings of the Surveys Division, May 6, 1942-September 7, 1942; 9/12/1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Preliminary Report. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, 9/18/1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Preliminary Report. Personal Identification with the War: Selected Interviews, 9/22/1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - R.25. Conceptions of the Role of America in World Affairs, 9/29/1942 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - R.25a. Summary Report. Conceptions of the Role of America in World Affairs, 9/29/1942 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - R.26. Conceptions of the Role of America in World Affairs: Part II, 9/29/1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - S.R.23. How the War Appears to Be Going: Trends, July to, September 1942; 9/29/1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Summary of Recent Findings Bearing on Labor Problems in War Industry, 9/30/1942
      - Preliminary Report. Personal Identification With the War: Some Preliminary Results, 10/03/1942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - S.R.24. Anti-British Attitudes of Negroes, 10/03/1942
      - Preliminary Report. Anti-Semitism--A Symptom of Disaffection, 10-8-42 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - S.R.25. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, Part I: Detroit, 10/08/1942 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - S.R.26. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, Part II: Mobile, 10/13/1942 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Conditions in Hawthorne, Nevada, 10/08/1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - R.27. Personal Identification With the War, 10/13/1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - R.27a. Summary Report. Personal Identification With the War, 10/13/1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - R.28. Governmental Compulsion During the War: Do People Want to Be Asked or to Be Told What to Do?, 10/13/1942 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - S.R.26. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, Part II: Mobile, 10/13/1942 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - S.R.27. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, Part III: Seattle, 10/15/1942 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - S.R.28. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, Part IV: Massena, N.Y., 10/15/1942 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Preliminary Report. Participation in the War Savings Program, 10/15/1942 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Preliminary Report. Civilian Participation in the War Effort: Selected Interviews, 10/17/1942 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - S.R.29. Baltimore Reactions to the Proposed "Share the Meat" Campaign, 10/21/1942 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - R.29. Attitudes Toward Jews in the United States, 10/27/1942 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - R.30. Political Anti/Semitism: A Study of Indoctrination, 10/27/1942 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Detroit People in Perspective: A Survey of Group Attitudes and Aspirations, 10/28/1943; 7 folders (Box 9, Folder 39-46)
      - S.R.30. Housing Problems in Four Production Communities, 10/30/1942 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Job Freezing in the Northwest's Lumber and Non-Ferrous Metals Industries, 11/02/1942 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - A Preliminary Impressionistic Report from Field Interviewers. The Social Dynamics of Detroit, 12/03/1942 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Survey of Intelligence materials
    - No. 6, January 16, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - No. 7, January 24, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - No. 8, February 2, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - No. 9, February 9, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - No. 10, February 16, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - No. 11, February 23, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - No. 12, March 2, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - No. 13, March 9, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - No. 14, March 16, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - No. 15, March 18, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - No. 16, March 25, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - No. 17, April 1, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - No. 18, April 8, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - No. 19, April 15, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - No. 20, April 22, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - No. 21, April 29, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 9)